Forms FORM-29827281-12:Test Assessment Report
This was a triumph
I'm making a note here:
HUGE SUCCESS.
It's hard to overstate
my satisfaction.
Aperture Science
We do what we must
because we can.
For the good of all of us.
Except the ones who are dead.
But there's no sense crying
over every mistake.
You just keep on trying
till you run out of cake.
And the Science gets done.
And you make a neat gun.
For the people who are
still alive.
Forms FORM-55551-5:Personnel File Addendum:
Dear &lt;&lt;Subject Name Here&gt;&gt;,
I'm not even angry.
I'm being
so
sincere right now.
Even though you broke my heart.
And killed
me.
And tore me to pieces.
And threw every piece
into a fire.
As they burned it hurt because
I was so happy for you!
Now these points of data
make a beautiful line
And we're out of beta.
We're releasing on time.
So I'm GLaD. I got burned.
Think of all the things we learned
for the people who are
still
alive.
Forms FORM-55551-6:Personnel File Addendum Addendum:
One last thing:
Go ahead and leave
me.
I think
I prefer
to stay
inside.
Maybe you'll find someone else
to help you.
Maybe Black
Mesa
...
THAT WAS A JOKE.
FAT CHANCE.
Anyway,
this cake is great.
It's so delicious and moist.
Look at me still talking
when there's Science to do.
When I look out there,
it makes me GLaD I'm not you.
I've experiments to run.
There is research to be done.
On the people who are
still
alive.
PS:
And believe me I am
still alive.
PPS:
I'm doing Science and I'm
still alive.
PPPS:
I feel FANTASTIC and I'm
still alive.
FINAL THOUGHT:
While you're dying I'll be
still alive.
FINAL THOUGHT PS:
And when you're dead I will be
still alive.
STILL ALIVE